Luca Palermo

Game Programmer

Address: Via Cintoia Bassa 26 50022, Greve In Chianti (FI)

Email: <u>luca.palermo98@gmail.com</u> Porfolio: <u>https://lucap998.github.io/</u>

Linkedin:https://www.linkedin.com/in/luca-palermo-ab7213

214/

EXPERIENCE

Instal, Florence— *Unity and mobile developer* February 2022 - Now

At Instal, I primarily worked on an in-game advertising SDK for Unity, featuring 3D banner ads rendered in a browser with a custom rendering system using native plugins and graphic APIs like OpenGL, Vulkan, and Metal. I also provided consulting for other companies, and made mobile and desktop applications, utilizing AR, VR, and computer vision technologies.

LionBridge, Remote, Freelance — *Game Tester*June 2020 - June 2021

At LionBridge, I worked as a Game Tester for online games. I primarily tested AAA games such as Crucible and New World by Amazon Games.

SKILLS

- Unity and C#.
- Android Studio and Java.
- Xcode and Swift.
- Unreal Engine and C++.

LANGUAGES

Italian - Native English - Advanced Japanese - Intermediate

ABOUT ME

My main hobby has been video games since I was 4 years old. My favorite series are The Legend of Zelda, Xenoblade Chronicles, Pokémon, and Super Smash Bros. I also really love Minecraft and

I played League of Legends for several years and reached the Platinum rank.

Additionally, I'm a big fan of rhythm games like Project Sekai and Beat Saber, where I always play at the highest difficulty.

I'm very interested in the world of technology in general, from computers to phones to anything that has electricity running through it, but my true passion will always be videogames.

EDUCATION

Digital Bros Academy, Game Dev, Remote *Diploma*

June 2024 - October 2024

This is an academy where I studied Unreal engine and worked on a

game in a team. I focused my attention particularly on the on the

C++ side of things, but I did blueprints as well.

TheSign Academy, Game Dev, Florence *Diploma*

2018 - 2021

At this academy, I followed a 3 years long course, where I learned

how to use Unity, and how to work together with designers and artists to create games. We also used Unreal Engine.

Istituto Calamandrei, Tech. School, Florence *Diploma*

2018

A technical institute, where I learned the basics of technology and programming.

Udemy courses, Online — *Certificates*

2021 - Now

I took various courses on Udemy in my free time to expand my knowledge and for passion:

- C++ 46 hours long course on pure C++, covering topics like polymorphism, inheritance, smart pointers, lambdas etc.
- Unreal Engine 35 hours long course on Unreal Engine, where I learned both the C++ side and the blueprint side of the engine, making some games like a top-down shooter, a third person shooter and more.

I also took some courses during my years working for Instal:

- Android 37 hours long course on android development with Android studio and Java.
- iOS 60 hours long course on iOS development with Xcode and Swift.